Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1947-2005; XIV.
  - Photographs (1995 Addition), 1958-1988; 2.
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 362)
      Photo 95: KLI in front of steps in Capital, 1983
      Photo 96: KLI at podium in House, 1983
      Photo 97: KLI at desk with moose statue, 1983
      Photo 98: Cactus decoration, 1983
      Photo 99: Silver Light, 1983
      Photo 100: Women in front of paintings, 1983
      Photo 101: Men in front of paintings, 1983
      Photo 102-103: KLI speaking in front of paintings, 1983
      Photo 104-105: KLI at art exhibit, 1983
      Photo 106-108: People at art exhibit, 1983
      Photo 109-111: KLI at party in home with Cathryn Irvis, 1983
      Photo 112-112C: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Tom Foerester ? - Redevelopment Authority, July 21, 1983
      Photo 113: KLI Mrs. Irvis with "Chemical People" (drug abuse programming), Governor Mrs. Thornburgh, September, 1983
      Photo 114: KLI, October, 1983
      Photo 115: KLI, Howard Hays Richard Caligiuri at opening of the New Pittsburgh Zoo, October 15, 1983
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 363)
      Photos 116-125A are accompanied by negatives and Photos 126-130A and Photos 136-138 are accompanied by pieces of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 116-125A: Democratic National Convention, August, 1984
      Photo 126-127: KLI with Ed Asner and others, 1984
      Photo 128: President Gerald Ford listening to KLI speak at the William Penn Hotel, 1984
      Photo 129: Market Square - KLI, Richard Caligiuri and Tom Foerester, 1984
      Photo 130-130A: Market Square - KLI, 1984
      Photo 131: 1984 Democratic National Convention - PA sign, 1984
      Photo 132-135: KLI at 1984 Democratic National Convention, 1984
      Photo 136-138: KLI Geraldine Ferraro in Harrisburg, 1984
      Photo 139: Judge Rufus S. Lynch at desk, November, 1984
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 364)
      Photos 140-142 are accompanied by pieces of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 140: KLI speaking at Temple University, 1985
      Photo 141-141: KLI at PA Jewish Coalition "Legislator of the Year Reception", 1985
      Photo 142: KLI at PA Jewish Coalition with Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Hal Bigler others, 1985
      Photo 143: KLI with Dick Cyert (Pres. of Carnegie Mellon University ) Mrs. Margaret Cyert at 1st Chamber of Commerce Statewide Dinner, autographed, 1985
      Photo 144-144B: KLI in House Chambers, January, 1985
      Photo 145-145B: KLI, January, 1985
      Photo 146: KLI Judge Loran Lewis (blurry), January 1, 1985
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 365)
      Photo 147: KLI in House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 148: KLI at podium in House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 149: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 150: KLI at podium in House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 151: KLI at his desk with fruit basket, January 1, 1985
      Photo 152: unidentified people in KLI's office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 153: KLI in his office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 154: KLI at his desk with fruit basket, January 1, 1985
      Photo 155: KLI opening gifts at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 156: KLI shaking hands with men in his office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 157: KLI sitting at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 158-159: KLI standing behind his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 160: KLI at his desk with fruit basket, January 1, 1985
      Photo 161: KLI on phone at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 162: KLI talking at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 163-164: Unidentified people in KLI's office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 165: KLI shaking hands with man in his office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 166: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 167: Judge woman in House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 168: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 169: KLI talking, January 1, 1985
      Photo 170: KLI at podium in the House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 171: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 172: KLI standing at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 173: 3 people on KLI's office sofa, January 1, 1985
      Photo 174-175: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 176: KLI at podium in the House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 177: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 178: KLI at podium in the House, January 1, 1985
      Photo 179: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 180: KLI, January 1, 1985
      Photo 181: KLI talking in his office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 182: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
      Photo 183: KLI shaking hands in his office, January 1, 1985
      Photo 184: KLI at his desk, January 1, 1985
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 366)
      Photo 185-185B: KLI, January 16, 1985
      Photo 186-186B: KLI child with gavel, January 16, 1985
      Photo 187-187A: KLI PA Legislative Black Caucus Plaque, February, 1985
      Photo 188: KLI at podium in House Chambers, February, 1985
      Photo 189: KLI in House Chambers, February, 1985
      Photo 190: KLI with young musicians, February, 1985
      Photo 191: KLI listening to speaker, February, 1985
      Photo 192-193A: KLI, February, 1985
      Photo 194-194A: KLI, Rep. Ruth Harper, Rep. Pete Truman, Rep. David P. Richardson PA Legislative Black Caucus Plaque, February, 1985
      Photo 195: KLI speaking at podium, February, 1985
      Photo 196: KLI, February, 1985
      Photo 197: KLI speaking, February, 1985
      Photo 198: KLI at podium, February, 1985
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 367)
      Photo 200 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 199-199A: Decorations for KLI's speech at Temple University, Spring 85
      Photo 200: KLI Rep. Raymond Book with his pages, May 13, 1985
      Photo 201: Woman (Janey Salary?) with dog on the Yellow Breeches (note on back), May 20,1985
      Photo 202: KLI Andrew Dinniman (Chester Co.), Democratic National Committee Members, 1985-1986
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 368)
      Photos 203-209 are accompanied by pieces of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 203-209: KLI on C-Span at Democratic National Convention, 1988
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 369)
      Photo 210: Contact Sheet: series of photos with KLI in House Chambers (see photo 326), 1988
      Photo 211: Contact Sheet: close-ups of KLI at podium in House Chambers (see photos 327-328), 1988
      Photo 212: Contact Sheet: close-ups of KLI holding scepter in front of flag (see photos 318, 321-325), 1988
      Photo 213: Contact sheet: close-ups of KLI holding scepter in front of bookshelves (see photos 319-320), 1988
      Photo 214: Contact sheet: close-ups of KLI holding scepter in front of bookshelves, 1988
      Photo 215: Democratic National Convention - Atlanta, GA - Clancy Myers (KLI's parliamentarian), Debbie Ellerman (Exec. Secretary), Susan Murin (Secretary to Clancy), July, 1988
      Photo 216: Democratic National Convention - Atlanta, GA - KLI (Chair of Credentials Committee), Clancy Myers (KLI's parliamentarian), Debbie Ellerman (Exec. Secretary), Susan Murin (Secretary to Clancy), Cleo Pheinbo? (KLI's Exec.), Cleo's granddaughter, July, 1988
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 370)
      Photo 217: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - Mr. James Getty dressed as Lincoln at podium in cemetery, November 19, 1988
      Photo 218-220: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - Congressman William F. Golding (U.S. House of Rep.) at podium in cemetery, November 19, 1988
      Photo 221: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - Chief Justice William F. Rehnquist at Gettysburg at Gettysburg College, November 19, 1988
      Photo 222: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - Gettysburg College, November 19, 1988
      Photo 223: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - KLI, November 19, 1988
      Photo 224-225: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - KLI riding on steam railroad, November 19, 1988
      Photo 226-227: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - KLI Rep. Donald Dorr. riding on steam railroad, November 19, 1988
      Photo 228: 125th Anniversary of Gettysburg Address, Gettysburg, PA - KLI Sam Hayes, November 19, 1988
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 371)
      Photos 229-233 are accompanied by pieces of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 229: Jennie boyfriend at prom, 1982
      Photo 230: Price Demplar, age 17, 1979
      Photo 231: Jennifer Demplar, age 16, 1979
      Photo 232: Kim Demplar, age 15, 1979
      Photo 233: Matt Demplar, age 7, 1979
      Photo 234: Matt Demplar, age 6, 1978?
      Photo 235: Matt Demplar, December, 1985
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 372)
      Photo 236: KLI Mrs. Cathy Irvis, no date
      Photo 237: KLI Mrs. Cathy Irvis being presented awards by same people as in previous photo, no date
      Photo 238-239: KLI Mrs. Cathy Irvis at a formal dinner, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 373)
      Photo 240: KLI shaking hands, no date
      Photo 241: KLI, no date
      Photo 242: unidentified group photo, no date
      Photo 243: KLI, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 374)
      Photo 244: KLI at podium, no date
      Photo 245: unidentified woman by podium, no date
      Photo 246-247: KLI and others at podium, no date
      Photo 248: KLI in large group with kids, no date
      Photo 249: KLI and others at podium, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 375)
      All photos in this folder are accompanied by negatives that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 250-251: KLI at his desk, no date
      Photo 252: KLI on stairs, no date
      Photo 253: Capital Rotunda, no date
      Photo 254: Statue at the bottom of stairs inside capital, no date
      Photo 255: KLI being filmed inside capital, no date
      Photo 256: unknown, no date
      Photo 257-260: KLI in his office, no date
      Photo 261: KLI at his desk, no date
      Photo 262: KLI in his office, no date
      Photo 263: KLI's office, no date
      Photo 264-265: KLI in his office, no date
      Photo 266: Mrs. Cathryn Irvis at KlI's desk, no date
      Photo 267-268: KLI in hotel room, no date
      Photo 269: Mrs. Cathryn Irvis in hotel room, no date
      Photo 270-272: unknown, no date
      Photo 273: KLI in hotel room, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 376)
      Photo 274: KLI in front of flags, October 4, 1984
      Photo 275 - 276: KLI with Geraldine Ferraro, October 4, 1984
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 377)
      Photo 277: Navy speakers, no date
      Photo 278: Navy speaker, no date
      Photo 279: Flag salute on submarine, no date
      Photo 280 - 281: Submarine with sailors, no date
      Photo 282-285: Submarine, no date
      Photo 286: Inside submarine, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 378)
      Photo 287-289: KLI group of people in front of airplane, no date
      Photo 290-291: KLI group of people inside airplane, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 379)
      Photo 292: Negro History Week display with KLI section, no date
      Photo 293: Negro History Week display, close-up of sculpture, no date
      Photo 294: Negro History Week display, close-up of KLI section, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 380)
      Photo 297 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 295: Photo of table with KLI at dinner, no date
      Photo 296: KLI Herb Fineman, no date
      Photo 297: KLI and woman in Hill District, no date
      Photo 298: KLI at desk, no date
      Photo 299: KLI at podium in House Chambers, no date
      Photo 300: KLI at signing ceremony, no date
      Photo 301-301A: KLI man handing over gavel, no date
      Photo 302: KLI unidentified man (possibly Fineman), no date
      Photo 303: KLI, Wesley Posvar unidentified man (autographed "To Lee Irvis" the best man in Harrisburg), no date
      Photo 304: KLI and Mrs. Cathy Irvis with children at ? School Art Exhibit, no date
      Photo 305: KLI, Sherri Lewis, Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Victor Mazyirin (Chief of Russian Delegation), no date
      Photo 306: KLI at outdoor rally?, sticker on the back for Rep. John E. Peterson, no date
      Photo 307: KLI sitting behind podium in House, no date
      Photo 308: KLI speaking to group, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 381)
      Photo 309-309B: KLI Mrs. Cathy Irvis at Legislative School Art Exhibit ribbon cutting ceremony, 1977
      Photo 310: KLI at podium, June 3, 1984
      Photo 311: KLI at Temple University School of Law, 1st annual Herbert Lowe Myers Distinguished Lecture, 1985
      Photo 312-314: KLI at podium in Holiday Inn, Gettysburg, PA for Memorial Day luncheon with Gen. William C. Westmoreland, May, 1988
      Photo 315: KLI at podium at the Democratic National Convention in Atlanta, 1988
      Photo 316: KLI at the House podium for Governor Casey's budget address, 1988
      Photo 317: KLI watching Governor Casey deliver his budget address, 1988
      Photo 318-325: KLI with scepter (see photo 212-213), 1988
      Photo 326-328: KLI at podium in House (see photo 210-211), 1988
      Photo 329: KLI walking w/unidentified man holding scepter at the dedication ceremony for the Capitol Addition, December 2, 1987
      Photo 330: KLI at podium at the dedication ceremony for the Capitol Addition, December 2, 1987
      Photo 331: KLI shaking hands with unidentified man in African garb, no date
      Photo 332-332A: KLI with others, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 382)
      Photo 333 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 333: Sculptor at work on statue of Martin Luther King, Jr. for Washington, D.C., no date
      Photo 334: Unidentified signing, no date
      Photo 335-337: Unidentified speakers at podium, no date
      Photo 338-338A: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, studio portrait, no date
      Photo 339-341: Mrs. Cathryn L. Irvis, studio portrait, no date
      Photo 342: Mrs. Cathy Irvis at formal dinner (see photos 236-239), no date
      Photo 343: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, no date
      Photo 344: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Tom Foerester, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 383)
      Photo 345: Mrs. Cathy Irvis and Marie Woods speaking at the William Penn Hotel, no date
      Photo 346: Mrs. Cathy Irvis speaking in Pittsburgh (view of city in window behind), no date
      Photo 347: Mrs. Cathy Irvis outdoor speaking engagement, no date
      Photo 348-350: Mrs. Cathy Irvis touring art studio, no date
      Photo 351: Thomas Foerster Jim Flaherty (Chairman) at desk with kids, no date
      Photo 352: Mrs. Cathy Irvis at signing ceremony ("Arts to the People"), no date
      Photo 353: Mrs. Cathy Irvis and others with painting, no date
      Photo 354: Mrs. Cathy Irvis and others with speaker at podium, no date
      Photo 355: Mrs. Cathryn L. Irvis at unidentified signing, no date
      Photo 356-357: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 384)
      Photo 358: Unidentified woman, no date
      Photo 359: KLI and Mrs. Kathryn Irvis, no date
      Photo 360: Greeting card with baby photo from the Sawyers (Roland, Aileen and Stephanie), no date
      Photo 361: Babe and Russ in front of the creek, July, 1958
      Photo 362: Mrs. Kathryn Irvis with children, no date
      Photo 363: Mrs. Kathryn Irvis and unidentified man, no date
      Photo 364: Public marketing event?, c. 1950s
      Photo 365: Mrs. Cathy Irvis in Harrisburg receiving NAACP (?) award for KLI, c. 1970s
      Photo 366: KLI, Mrs. Kathryn "Kitten" Irvis, Lois Watson, and Ken Vaughn at the Harrisburger Hotel for KLI's swearing-in, January, 1959
      Photo 367-368: KLI and Mrs. Kathryn Irvis at a formal dinner, c. 1950s
      Photo 369: Slide of KLI and Mrs. Kathryn Irvis at a formal dinner, c. 1950s
      Photo 370: KLI, no date
    - Photos (Box 89, Folder 384)
      Photo 371: Summer 1951
      Photo 372: DA's Office, 1957
      Photo 373: KLI at Desk, Harrisburg, Summer 1963
      Photo 374: KLI, 1950s
      Photo 375: KLI (photo taken by Teenie Harris), 1960s
  - Photographs (2010 Addition), 1947-2005; 3.
    This subseries contains a number of images that correspond to subject titles of aforementioned subseries. Some of these subjects include African American interests, Cathryn Irvis, Community involvement, Democratic Party involvement, Legal Career, Legislative Career, and Personal. In addition to the subseries listed above, the Photographs subseries also contains images of Irvis at various events throughout his career. In this subseries, the photographs are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Africa, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - African American Interests, Martin Luther King Center, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - African American Interests, NAACP East, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - African American Interests, NAACP Youth Award, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - African American Interests, Urban League, undated (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - African American Interests, Urban League Staff, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Cathryn Irvis, Award, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Cathryn Irvis, Birthday, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Cathryn Irvis, BWPC, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Cathryn Irvis, BWPC Photo Album, 1980-1987 (Box 137)
    - Cathryn Irvis, International Year of the Child, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Cathryn Irvis, International Year of the Child, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Community, ACT 101, undated (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Community, Annual Community Involvement Awards Dinner Photo Album, 1971 (Box 132)
    - Community, Clarion University, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Community, Cleveland Strong Men and Women, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Community, Community College of Allegheny County, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Community, Dedication of the Irvis Reading Room, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Community, Edinboro University, undated (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Community, Gettysburg College, undated (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Community, K. Leroy Irvis Towers, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Community, Lincoln University, undated (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Community, Lock Haven State College, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Community, Martin Luther King Jr. East Busway, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Community, Night of a Thousand Stars, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Community, Penn State, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Community, Pittsburgh Hyatt House, undated (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Community, Pittsburgh Opportunities Industrialization Center Inc., Photo Album, 1979-1982 (Box 135)
    - Community, Sickle Cell, undated (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Community, Temple University, undated (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Community, University of Pittsburgh, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Community, Westchester State College, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Democratic Party Involvement, undated (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - Events, undated (Box 118, Folder 31)
    - Events, undated (Box 118, Folder 32)
    - Events, undated (Box 118, Folder 33)
    - Events, undated (Box 118, Folder 34)
    - Legislative, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 35)
    - Legislative, Airport Groundbreaking, undated (Box 118, Folder 36)
    - Legislative, Bicentennial Joint Session, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - Legislative, Bicentennial Joint Session, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 38)
    - Legislative, Legal, 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 39)
    - Legislative, Legal, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 40)
    - Legislative, Bill Signing, 1971-1976 (Box 118, Folder 41)
    - Legislative, Legislative Black Caucus, 1983-1984 (Box 118, Folder 42)
    - Legislative, the Carters, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - Legislative, Carter Quito Trip, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 44)
    - Legislative, Clairborne, Loretta, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 45)
    - Legislative, Dedication of the Speaker K. Leroy Irvis Office Building, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 46)
    - Legislative, Democratic Caucus, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 47)
    - Legislative, Election Activities, undated (Box 118, Folder 48)
    - Legislative, Events, undated (Box 118, Folder 49)
    - Legislative, Events, undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Legislative, Events, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Legislative, Harrisburg Office, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Legislative, Heritage Road, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Building, 1986-1987 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives, Building Dedication, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives, Building Dedication, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives, Floor, undated (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives, Floor, undated (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, undated (Oversize 192, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1963 (Oversize 193)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1965-1966 (Oversize 194, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1967-1968 (Oversize 195, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1971 (Oversize 196, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1973 (Oversize 197, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, House of Representatives Session, 1984-1985 (Oversize 198, Drawer 16-11)
    - Legislative, Larry Howard Taping, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Legislative, Lion of Pennsylvania Premiere Photo Album, 2004 (Box 140)
    - Legislative, Panama Canal, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Legislative, Portraits, undated (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Legislative, Staff, undated (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Legislative, Staff, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Legislative, Staff, undated (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Legislative, USS Pittsburgh Commissioning, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Legislative, 266th Pennsylvania House of Representatives Plaque, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Personal, ARCS, 1991, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Personal, Art, 1986-1997 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Personal, Family in Albany, New York, 2004 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, undated (Box 129)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, 1957-1977 (Box 130)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, c. 1960-1970 (Box 131)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, 1972 (Box 133)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, c. 1980 (Box 136)
    - Personal, Family Photo Album, 1989, 1990 (Box 138)
    - Personal, Family Vacation Photo Album, 1972 (Box 134)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Friends and Family, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Personal, Katharyne Irvis, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Personal, Model Airplanes, 1972, undated (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Personal, Paris, undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Personal, Paris, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Personal, Portraits, undated (Box 120, Folder 9)